[
  {
    "question": "Convert 59.7210 to BCD.",
    "choices": [
      "111011",
      "01011001.01110010",
      "1110.11",
      "0101100101110010"
    ],
    "answer": "01011001.01110010"
  },
  {
    "question": "Convert hexadecimal value C1 to binary.",
    "choices": [
      "11000001",
      "1000111",
      "111000001",
      "111000100"
    ],
    "answer": "11000001"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many binary digits are required to count to 10010?",
    "choices": [
      "100",
      "3",
      "7",
      "2"
    ],
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "The binary number for octal 458 is ________.",
    "choices": [
      "100010",
      "100100",
      "110101",
      "100101"
    ],
    "answer": "100101"
  },
  {
    "question": "A binary number's value changes most drastically when the ________ is changed.",
    "choices": [
      "frequency",
      "duty cycle",
      "LSB",
      "MSB"
    ],
    "answer": "MSB"
  },
  {
    "question": "The sum of 11101 + 10111 equals ________.",
    "choices": [
      "100001",
      "100100",
      "110011",
      "110100"
    ],
    "answer": "110100"
  },
  {
    "question": "The sum of 1111 + 1111 in binary equals",
    "choices": [
      "11111",
      "0000",
      "2222",
      "11110"
    ],
    "answer": "11110"
  },
  {
    "question": "One hex digit is sometimes referred to as a(n):",
    "choices": [
      "nibble",
      "grouping",
      "instruction",
      "byte"
    ],
    "answer": "nibble"
  },
  {
    "question": "Assign the proper odd parity bit to the code 111001.",
    "choices": [
      "0011111",
      "1111001",
      "0111111",
      "1111011"
    ],
    "answer": "1111001"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is an invalid BCD code?",
    "choices": [
      "0011",
      "1001",
      "0101",
      "1101"
    ],
    "answer": "1101"
  },
  {
    "question": "Convert binary 111111110010 to hexadecimal.",
    "choices": [
      "2FE16",
      "EE216",
      "FD216",
      "FF216"
    ],
    "answer": "FF216"
  },
  {
    "question": "Convert the following binary number to decimal.100110102",
    "choices": [
      "155",
      "157",
      "153",
      "154"
    ],
    "answer": "154"
  },
  {
    "question": "Convert the following binary number to decimal.010112",
    "choices": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "15",
      "35"
    ],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "question": "Convert the following octal number to decimal 178",
    "choices": [
      "51",
      "82",
      "15",
      "57"
    ],
    "answer": "15"
  },
  {
    "question": "Convert binary 01001110 to decimal.",
    "choices": [
      "4E",
      "78",
      "116",
      "76"
    ],
    "answer": "78"
  },
  {
    "question": "The difference of 1000 − 100 equals",
    "choices": [
      "100",
      "110",
      "101",
      "111"
    ],
    "answer": "100"
  },
  {
    "question": "Convert the binary number 1100 to Gray code.",
    "choices": [
      "1010",
      "100",
      "0011",
      "1001"
    ],
    "answer": "1010"
  },
  {
    "question": "3428 is the decimal value for which of the following binary-coded decimal (BCD) groupings?",
    "choices": [
      "011010010000010",
      "11010001001000",
      "110100001101010",
      "11010000101000"
    ],
    "answer": "11010000101000"
  },
  {
    "question": "The difference of 111 – 001 equals ________.",
    "choices": [
      "001",
      "110",
      "111",
      "100"
    ],
    "answer": "110"
  },
  {
    "question": "Convert the Gray code 1011 to binary.",
    "choices": [
      "1011",
      "1010",
      "1101",
      "0100"
    ],
    "answer": "1101"
  }
]